Hello, my friends, and welcome to exercise number 41 in this exercise, we are asked to print the
notes of link and place that we have created before, so please go back to the previous video, if you
would, if you miss anything.
So we have created a another object called had and we have created the Class A..
OK.
And the main activity in the main method we have created and link that nodes together.
OK, so the first note with reference to the next note as second note and the second the next to it
will give us a third.
Not the first note contains one.
The second note contains two and the third note would contain number three.
So we have seen this in the lecture.
How to do that and see and I will make these make a real word that programming because many of of people,
many of students have requested to make real examples real war and without making just copy and paste
the code, they need that real running of the program.
So how to do that?
We need to create a function that prints the content of their link, at least starting from health.
So this function function that prints the content of link list starting
from hand.
OK.
This this consecutive exercises, we are just compacting them into a one file so you can download the
zip code in the resources and on every lesson.
OK, so so how to do that?
We create public void trend list.
And in this list we will create a nod here and equal to hat.
OK will create it as the wild and does not equal to null.
OK.
This is how we check that we didn't reach there last and the end of the link atlas system that out dot
print n.
We need from and so the not as I told you, it is separated and contains two parts.
The first part contains the data and the second part contains the reference.
We don't need that reference.
We need to print the data.
So MN Dot, we have next and we have data data of Typekit and next of Typekit.
Not we don't need them next and don't need the reference.
So and data plus or and data.
It's good.
Know how to move the cursor from and does not equal to knowledge.
We need to move the cursor to the next, not by calling an equal and the next.
OK, this jumping, this will jump that and the iterator from the first nod to the second node to the
third and so on to tell reaching an equal to none.
So when am equal to null?
And then when they're not equal to null, then a break from this loop and don't print any thing?
OK?
In order to test this method, we go to the main method and we will.
I would put exercise for two one printing.
Printing link at best and just call list DOT.
Brent list.
OK.
OK, guys, it's very simple.
Let's run and see.
Okay.
We need to change the configurations and configuration.
It's not hello.
It's linked list.
Apply and click OK, because I have deleted data.
OK, and here we go.
These are then data that are stored inside, then nuts.
OK, so our linked list contains three notes.
The first one contains data.
Number one, the second contain number two and the third contain number three.
And it's very.